bankoftexas.com 2008-09-13

# PRIVACY POLICY

**PRIVACY POLICY**

You have entrusted us with your personal information and we recognize our obligation to keep information about you secure and confidential. Therefore, to protect and maintain this relationship, we have enacted this privacy policy to maintain the confidentiality of the information you have shared with us. This policy covers your nonpublic personal information (Customer Information), which means personally identifiable information about a consumer's current or former relationship with us or any of our affiliated companies. This policy does not apply to the Mortgage Division which has its own privacy policy.

****
  1. **CATEGORIES OF CUSTOMER INFORMATION WE COLLECT**   
The Customer Information we collect is categorized below:
    1. Information you provide to us on applications and through other means, such as your assets, income and other debt. 
    2. Information about your transactions and account experience with us or our family of companies, such as your account balance and payment history, or information about our communications with you, such as a request for a copy of a check and our response.
    3. Information from a consumer report, such as information regarding your creditworthiness or credit history.
    4. Information from other outside sources, such as verifying representations made by you regarding employment history, loan or credit card balances, or your property insurance coverage.
    5. Other general information we obtain about you that is not assembled for the purpose of determining your eligibility for credit, insurance, employment or other products or services you request, such as demographic information.
  2. **CIRCUMSTANCES UNDER WHICH WE SHARE WITH AFFILIATED COMPANIES**   
We may share all five types of Customer Information, described in Section I, among our affiliated companies. Our affiliated companies include financial institutions, securities broker-dealers, insurance companies and trust companies. 

We occasionally receive medical or health information about a customer, for example, if a customer applies for insurance from us. If we do receive medical or health information about a customer, we will not share it among our affiliated companies, except as necessary to maintain accounts, process transactions or provide services the customer has requested or initiated.

  3. **CIRCUMSTANCES UNDER WHICH WE MAY SHARE INFORMATION WITH NONAFFILIATED THIRD PARTIES**  
We may share all five types of Customer Information described in Section I with nonaffiliated third parties. The nonaffiliated third parties may include (i) financial service providers, for example, insurance companies, mortgage bankers, and securities broker-dealers; (ii) nonfinancial companies, for example, check printing and data processing companies and companies that perform services for us; (iii) financial institutions with whom we have a joint marketing agreement, (iv) credit bureaus and similar organizations. We may share all five types of Customer Information with such nonaffiliated third parties for the following purposes, for example: 
    1. To provide you products and services you have requested
    2. To process a transaction initiated by you
    3. To perform services for us pursuant to a contract,
    4. To perform according to a joint marketing agreement with another financial institution
    5. To respond to a subpoena, a fraud investigation, or other legal process
    6. To record deeds of trust or mortgages in public records
    7. To conduct an audit or examination
    8. To provide a service with your consent, including the case where you have given someone your power of attorney or other written authorization to act on your behalf, or as otherwise permitted by law.
  4. **DIRECT MARKETING**
  
We would like to keep you informed about valuable offers that help you manage your finances. Although you can choose not to receive marketing offers from us by direct mail, telephone and/or e-mail. 

This preference applies to offers from us about products, services and special offers that we think may be of interest to you.

If you choose not to hear from us, you may not receive offers about products, services and special offers that may be of value to you.

If you elect not to receive product information by email, telephone or mail, you will continue to:

    1. Be contacted as necessary to service your account
    2. Receive marketing information included with your statements and when you visit us at an ATM or Online

Since some marketing programs may already be in progress, it may take four to six weeks for your preferences to be fully effective.

  5. **CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY**
  
The security of your personal Customer Information is very important to us. We restrict access to your Customer Information to those employees that have a legitimate business reason to conduct business on your account. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your Customer Information. 
  6. **YOUR CHOICES**  
This section describes your choices. Please remember we do not sell or share client information with marketers outside our affiliated companies. No action is required for this benefit. We will continue to protect your personal information regardless of your privacy choices.

**_Telling us your preferences:_**  
_Sharing among the affiliated companies_  
If you prefer that we not share your Customer Information with our affiliated companies, we will honor your request. Simply complete the instructions within the Opt Out Request Form and select the box beside the heading of Do not share my information with your affiliated companies.

_Direct Marketing_  
You may also request that we not contact you about direct marketing offers through any or all of the following methods of communication: Telephone, Mail or Email. Simply check the applicable boxes within the Opt Out Request Form. Please remember, by selecting these boxes you may not receive valuable special offers.

  7. **MAKING SURE INFORMATION IS ACCURATE**
  
Keeping your account information accurate and up to date is very important. If you ever find that your account information is incomplete, inaccurate or not current, please write us at the address listed on your account statement, bank records, or other documentation. We will promptly update or correct any erroneous information. 
  8. **HOW TO LIMIT OUR USE OF YOUR CUSTOMER INFORMATION**
  
We have a right to share Customer Information, described in Section I, about our customers or former customers with our affiliated companies and with nonaffiliated third parties as described in Section III. If you prefer that we not share your Customer Information with our affiliated companies, we will honor your request (except we may continue to share transaction and experience information authorized under the Fair Credit Reporting Act). You may make such a request by the method described below. We will honor your request throughout our affiliated companies. 
    * Fill out the Opt Out Request form provided.
    * In order to ensure that we accurately reflect your request, please provide your full name, address, social security number, and telephone number
    * Detach and mail the Opt Out Request Form to: Bank of Texas, Attention: CRF-BTC 1E, P.O. Box 29775, Dallas, TX 75229-0775.
    * This request will apply to information from applications, consumer reports and other outside sources only.
    * If there is more than one borrower on your account, we will honor the Opt Out Request for all borrowers of record on your account.
    * Please allow six to eight weeks to be fully effective.

| **OPT OUT REQUEST FORM**  
---  
Please complete the following information. All information must be provided in order to process the form. If you have previously opted out, there is no need to respond.  
| Name:|   
---|---  
Address:|   
City:|   
State, ZIP:|   
Telephone:|   
Social Security Number:|   
Signature:|   
| | Do not share my information with your affiliated companies.  
---|---  
| _E-mail_ : I do not want to receive offers from Bank of Texas via email about products, services and special offers.  
| _Telephone_ : I do not want to receive offers from Bank of Texas via telephone about products, services and special offers.  
| _Mail_ : I do not want to receive offers from Bank of Texas via mail about products, services and special offers.  
  
**Mail to:**  
Bank of Texas  
Attn: CRF/EFT Department  
P.O. Box 29775  
Dallas, TX 75229-0775

Please allow six to eight weeks to be fully effective.
